<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Albany Academy]]></title><description><![CDATA[Albany Academy]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/aa-news</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:21:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Student-Athletes Compete in Disney Fall Junior Open]]></title><description><![CDATA[It has been an incredible start to the new academic school year with 12 students traveling to Orlando to compete in the Disney Fall...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/student-athletes-compete-in-disney-fall-junior-open</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6346c78313cc0617b31cd348</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 14:12:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_2d7c4e7a959c42008a56d08a981605b1~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been an incredible start to the new academic school year with 12 students traveling to Orlando to compete in the Disney Fall Junior Open.</p>

<p>In the Girls 14-18 division, Annika Kohoutek achieved her first hole-in-one in round two on hole 12. Annika started at Albany Academy this academic year and posted scores of 75 and 72 to finish in third place. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_05c93d1c0e89492cb076376070856898~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>In the Girls Under-13 division, Mila Zalsman won her age division on her debut. Mila has only recently joined Albany Golf Academy with this being her first 36-hole tournament as part of the team. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_e0382b78b4fc4423bdd1f3576a1af242~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>In the Boys 16-18 division, Alex Rowland finished in first place with scores of 73 and 67, winning by three strokes with a total of 4-under-par for the tournament. Alex posted a flawless 5-under-par, bogey-free round to clinch the victory and his personal best score.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_7ff0d5a703c44ce3bbfae6f44066ce22~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>In the Boys 11-13 division, Aidan Gorospe won by 6 shots with scores of 76 and 70. A fantastic 2-under-par final round sealed the deal consisting of four birdies. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_fc7f4db61fc74c25b6c2dc70cd7dbc05~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emily Mayne is the 34th Caribbean Amateur Junior Girls Champion]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is a huge moment and I could not be any happier for you @emilymaynegolf, you deserve this moment! I am a very proud coach, this year...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/emily-mayne-is-the-34th-caribbean-amateur-junior-girls-champion</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62c493251ccd85871ee3233c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 19:38:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d5e4a0_4d4ca3bd19264dc8911bf863a2b5b0b3~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a huge moment and I could not be any happier for you @emilymaynegolf, you deserve this moment!</p>

<p>I am a very proud coach, this year has been very challenging for Em in many ways on and off the course but she kept fighting, working through a tough period to come out the other end, loving and enjoying her golf again. This is testimony to her huge heart and character of person. Congratulations again Em, enjoy this moment</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d5e4a0_4d4ca3bd19264dc8911bf863a2b5b0b3~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anne Fernandez Wins The Coastal Carolina Summer Junior Open]]></title><description><![CDATA[Shooting rounds of 65 -5 and 71 +1 for a -4 total and 23 shots ahead of second place . Anne had 13 birdies, 18 pars, 5 bogeys and 1...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/anne-fernandez-wins-the-coastal-carolina-summer-junior-open</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62c4928ad0b0bc2454a0782a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 19:37:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d5e4a0_52ea63e573fc4111bba460c6d60cac30~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_768,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shooting rounds of 65 -5 and 71 +1 for a -4 total and 23 shots ahead of second place .</p>

<p>Anne had 13 birdies, 18 pars, 5 bogeys and 1 double (due to OB).</p>

<p>Onwards and Upwards as she will prepare for her AJGA Qualifier in a few days. Back to work tomorrow preparing and working on areas that need to tidy up following what we’ve learned from this tournament.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/d5e4a0_52ea63e573fc4111bba460c6d60cac30~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_768,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anne Fernandez Wins the Upstate Junior Classic Championship]]></title><description><![CDATA[Congratulations to student-athlete Anne Fernandez who won the Upstate Junior Classic Championship in style at Smithfields Country Club....]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/anne-fernandez-wins-the-upstate-junior-classic-championship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62a223b26d9cc20f41eed666</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:49:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_02bd958c2a99458ab1aae0f52d1052f6~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_824,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to student-athlete Anne Fernandez who won the Upstate Junior Classic Championship in style at Smithfields Country Club. </p>

<p>Despite the course being set up shorter than expected, Anne used her superb course management skills to play smart and pick targets relative to her dispersion patterns. </p>

<p>Anne shot rounds of 1-under-par and 2-under-par to finish 3-under-par for the tournament, boasting the lowest score of the entire competition from boys and girls.</p>

<p>Congratulations to Anne on this victory and best of luck as she prepares for the U.S. Girls' Qualifier in Columbia, SC.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_02bd958c2a99458ab1aae0f52d1052f6~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_824,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Luke Block Wins 2022 Albany Club Championship]]></title><description><![CDATA[Congratulations to Luke Block on successfully defending the 2022 Albany Men's Club Championship this past weekend. Congratulations are...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/luke-block-wins-2022-albany-club-championship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6266d31e3d6ac252c6142b1e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:00:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_7d6f821c09894e46a24d7d918b26a936~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_640,h_640,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to Luke Block on successfully defending the 2022 Albany Men's Club Championship this past weekend. Congratulations are also in order to Harry White who finished in 2nd place in the Junior Club Championship.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Student-Athletes See Success at Central Florida Spring Junior Open]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nine Albany Academy students traveled to compete in the Central Florida Spring Junior Open at DeBary Golf and Country Club, a golf course...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/student-athletes-see-success-at-central-florida-spring-junior-open</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6266d11d7d14e2288777dd1d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 16:57:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_ca029691999143e780e33a5f0aba2e03~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nine Albany Academy students traveled to compete in the Central Florida Spring Junior Open at DeBary Golf and Country Club, a golf course with extremely slick and undulating greens and difficult pin placements. </p>

<p>In the Girls 14-18 division, Holly McLean captured the victory on the second sudden-death playoff hole. Mattea Issa finished 3rd and demonstrated tremendous ball-striking all weekend. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_ca029691999143e780e33a5f0aba2e03~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>In the Boys 14-15 Division, Alex Rowland finished with a level-par first round and +2 final round, won his division, and was the lowest scoring player from any age division in the tournament. Walker Faust finished in 3rd place and learned a lot about his game and tendency under tournament conditions. </p>

<p>In the Boys 11-13 Division, Kerrington Rolle narrowly missed out on his second win and finished runner up.</p>

<p>Congratulations to all Albany Academy students on this very successful trip.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grace Crawford Wins the 2022 R&#38;A U16 Amateur Championship]]></title><description><![CDATA[Student-athlete Grace Crawford secured back-to-back victories after finishing with an eagle on the final hole to claim victory in the R&#38;A...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/grace-crawford-wins-the-2022-r-a-u16-amateur-championship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6266cf1c536221466d6bd8d4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 16:46:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_2b2d9d97b57e4eb695b22a534240bcc8~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_688,h_618,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Student-athlete Grace Crawford secured back-to-back victories after finishing with an eagle on the final hole to claim victory in the R&A Girls’ U16 Amateur Championship at Enville.   Last week Grace won the Helen Holm Scottish Women’s Open at Royal Troon and the North Berwick which was yet another notable career triumph. </p>

<p>Congratulations to Grace on two incredible performances that are credited to countless hours of hard work.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grace Crawford Wins Helen Holm Scottish Women’s Open]]></title><description><![CDATA[Congratulations to student-athlete Grace Crawford who is the Helen Holm Scottish Women's Open Champion for 2022. The championship was...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/grace-crawford-wins-helen-holm-scottish-women-s-open</link><guid isPermaLink="false">625d62faa264d2a53e7f1dd2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 13:14:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_44f61a5115ac481c8f99ca043c61d886~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to student-athlete Grace Crawford who is the Helen Holm Scottish Women's Open Champion for 2022. The championship was hosted at Royal Troon and Portland in Scotland providing a stern test to 110 of the best women's players in Europe. </p>

<p>The courses were playing 6,300 yards with strong winds throughout the championship, and on the final day, it was a three-club wind with gusts making play extremely difficult for all. </p>

<p>Grace played incredible golf shooting rounds of 2-under-par and 2-over-par at Portland Golf Club, followed by a final round at Royal Troon of 4-under-par for a total of -4 (212). </p>

<p>Congratulations again to Grace on this incredible international victory.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_44f61a5115ac481c8f99ca043c61d886~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Several Student-Athletes Celebrate Recent Wins]]></title><description><![CDATA[Congratulations are in order for several Albany Academy student-athletes on their recent successes on the course. Luke Block won the...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/several-student-athletes-celebrate-recent-wins</link><guid isPermaLink="false">624afe9659432da46c2c0e74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 14:39:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_312cc8051b044b2abc1892d648195f83~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Congratulations are in order for several Albany Academy student-athletes on their recent successes on the course.</p>

<p>Luke Block won the 16-18 Division at The Jekyll Island Junior Open in Georgia. He shot a first-round score of 71 (1-under-par) and a final round score of 68 (4-under-par) for a total score of 5-under-par.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_312cc8051b044b2abc1892d648195f83~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Holly McLean recently competed in the HJGT hosted at Saddlebrook Golf Club and won the girls 14-18 division with scores of 71 and 68 to win by 4 shots and finish 1-under-par.</p>

<p>As we start spring break, Albany Academy players teed it up at The Bahamas Junior National Championships hosted at Ocean Club Golf Course.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_283a6c5ec13142e992670fca8d8f0fd6~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_768,h_768,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>In the Girls 10-13 division, Lilly Bisterzo captured the trophy with a 1-shot lead.</p>

<p>In the Boys 13-Under division, Harry White won his group by a margin of 14 strokes.</p>

<p>In the Boys 10-13 division, Aidan Gorospe won with a 5 shot margin over fellow Albany Academy player Kerrington Rolle who finished runner up.</p>

<p>In the Boys 14-15 division, Olly White won by 3 shots.</p>

<p>In the Boys 16-18 division, Heath Kane won by  6 shots, with Jaden Ward finishing runner up and Alex Dupuch finishing in third place.</p>

<p>Congratulations to all student-athletes on these incredible achievements! </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Student-Athletes Compete in Alaqua Junior Open]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last weekend, our student-athletes traveled to Lake Mary, FL to compete in the Alaqua Junior Open. All players were faced with unusual...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/student-athletes-compete-in-alaqua-junior-open</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6239c68fb7e9f6160e298c63</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 12:57:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_072e8012d5614b819602f9936db01da5~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last weekend, our student-athletes traveled to Lake Mary, FL to compete in the Alaqua Junior Open. All players were faced with unusual conditions over the two days, including playing on a water-logged course without the ability to lift clean and place mud balls. </p>

<p>Congratulations to Kerrington Rolle on winning his first international tournament this past weekend. Without fail Kerrington has remained focused on the process and conducts himself impeccably both at training and on the course.</p>

<p>We also congratulate Holly McLean who nearly captured the win, having to play a sudden-death playoff on the 10th hole. Holly lead after the first round and kept battling through to the very end.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_072e8012d5614b819602f9936db01da5~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holly McLean Wins National Amateur Championship]]></title><description><![CDATA[Student-athlete Holly McLean is the 2022 Champion Golfer after winning the Cayman Islands National Amateur Championship. Holly played...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/holly-mclean-wins-national-amateur-championship</link><guid isPermaLink="false">622fbbc2deb44e46d79d9b35</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 22:06:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_83dd6baa74054ba6a55fabf725b92119~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Student-athlete Holly McLean is the 2022 Champion Golfer after winning the Cayman Islands National Amateur Championship. </p>

<p>Holly played great golf in very challenging winds shooting +3 in the first round which put her in the lead going into the final round. Holly shot a marvelous 2-under-par in the final round to secure the win.</p>

<p>Congratulations Holly on this achievement that was made possible by your hard work on and off the course. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_83dd6baa74054ba6a55fabf725b92119~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Student-Athletes Compete at the Village Golf Club in Palm Beach, FL ]]></title><description><![CDATA[A jam-packed trip to the Village Golf Club in Palm Beach, FL was full of new and interesting experiences for the Albany Academy...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/student-athletes-compete-at-the-village-golf-club-in-palm-beach-fl</link><guid isPermaLink="false">621cfdcfaf5d83647abd2767</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 16:56:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_b3bf3226e8e147949db585e8cb77b2d4~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A jam-packed trip to the Village Golf Club in Palm Beach, FL was full of new and interesting experiences for the Albany Academy student-athletes. </p>

<p>At this venue, course management was paramount to navigate around the small greens and tree-lined fairways. The temperatures, around 83 degrees, with a brisk wind swirling around the golf course created a very tricky challenge for the players. </p>

<p>In the girls 14-18 category, Grace Crawford took her second win with an extremely impressive second round of 68 (-4) low score of the week, following her first round of 74. Anne Fernandez finished runner up posting two consistent rounds of 74 and 75. </p>
<p>Holly McLean finished in third place after holding the overnight lead with a score of 72 on day one.</p>

<p>In the boys 14-15 category, Alex Rowland took home the first place trophy with scores of 74 and 77. Oliver White finished runner-up playing to his strengths and utilizing a plan that allows him to navigate a difficult golf course. </p>

<p>Congratulations to all 15 Albany Academy students who competed in all the various categories. A special thank you to GFORE for the new clothing that allowed the players to look and feel their best.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Student-Athletes Travel to Compete at Westchester Country Club]]></title><description><![CDATA[Grace Crawford, Anne Fernandez, Emily Mayne, Holly McLean, Mattea Issa and Alex Rowland traveled to Boynton Beach, Florida for the HJGT...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/student-athletes-travel-to-compete-at-westchester-country-club</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61f99280329cd6b422d0517e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 20:17:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_24382aed438d464386c446b59ff2cb3b~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grace Crawford, Anne Fernandez, Emily Mayne, Holly McLean, Mattea Issa and Alex Rowland traveled to Boynton Beach, Florida for the HJGT at Westchester Country Club. </p>

<p>In the Girls 14-18 division, Grace Crawford earned first place in her first trip to Florida, winning her first HJGT in her Academy debut trip. Emily Mayne finished runner up narrowly missing out on a playoff. Tied for 3rd, Holly McLean posted two consistent rounds and Anne Fernandez with a strong second round score to move her back up the leaderboard. </p>
<p>Finishing tied for 5th, Mattea Issa navigated Westchester demonstrating amazing course management skills. </p>

<p>In the Boys 16-18 Division, Alex Rowland finished in 2nd place and narrowly missed out on victory after a two-hole playoff with putts agonizingly shaving the edge of the hole, and Heath Kane finished strong in 4th place.</p>

<p>Congratulations to all the players who competed!</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Luke Block Earns Runner-Up Finish]]></title><description><![CDATA[At Oak Point Kiawah Island Junior Open, Luke Block placed second in very cold and windy conditions, narrowly missing out on a play-off...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/luke-block-earns-runner-up-finish</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61f9909311246a8e458af762</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_4e6259ba8e034d89b371281b96f3f40f~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At Oak Point Kiawah Island Junior Open, Luke Block placed second in very cold and windy conditions, narrowly missing out on a play-off for the title. </p>

<p>Demonstrating true maturity and sportsmanship, Luke’s playing partner got up and down from a hazard holing a 12-foot putt to win. Luke has developed into both an amazing player and a mature and incredible human being. </p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_4e6259ba8e034d89b371281b96f3f40f~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Luke Block Earns Top 3 Finish]]></title><description><![CDATA[Luke Block kicked off the 2022 season with a top 3 finish. He traveled to compete in The Savannah Junior Open hosted by The Club at...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/luke-block-earns-top-3-finish</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61f1be1032701c0017e38925</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:38:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_b1f23cb8f2434b6498eca003c19b3ba4~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Luke Block kicked off the 2022 season with a top 3 finish. He traveled to compete in The Savannah Junior Open hosted by The Club at Savannah Harbor. Despite facing cold conditions, Luke shot rounds of 76 and 77 which earned him a top 3 finish. Congratulations to Luke on this achievement and a wonderful start to the season.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_b1f23cb8f2434b6498eca003c19b3ba4~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holly McLean Commits to Oklahoma University]]></title><description><![CDATA[Albany Academy student-athlete Holly McLean has verbally accepted a full-ride scholarship to become a part of Oklahoma University’s...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/holly-mclean-commits-to-oklahoma-university</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61f1bcbca15ee200163ef96f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:31:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_0127f019508241f997fe7a58c47deea8~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_568,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Albany Academy student-athlete Holly McLean has verbally accepted a full-ride scholarship to become a part of Oklahoma University’s women’s golf team. Holly has worked tirelessly and pushed herself on and off the course to achieve her dream goal of playing Division I college golf. Congratulations to Holly on this tremendous achievement. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_0127f019508241f997fe7a58c47deea8~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_568,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Walker Faust Scores a Personal Best]]></title><description><![CDATA[Student-athlete Walker Faust kicked off the New Year with a personal best performance shooting under-par on the last nine holes to secure...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/walker-faust-scores-a-personal-best</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61d34a4e1dbb5700164fc655</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:13:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_b15e87f7d5da48a9bc16e6a45363dab8~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Student-athlete Walker Faust kicked off the New Year with a personal best performance shooting under-par on the last nine holes to secure 2nd place. Walker shot rounds of 81 and 71 on a very challenging golf course at Wild Dunes Resort Links in South Carolina.</p>

<p>This par-70 course is known for being very tough with hazards on every hole and very narrow fairways. This weekend provided an extra tough test in harsh conditions with about 15-25 mph winds all day. </p>

<p>After a challenging first round, Walker reminded himself to stay patient, remain disciplined and play the easiest shot possible. This resulted in his lowest score to date and a standout performance with the lowest score of the day in his division.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_b15e87f7d5da48a9bc16e6a45363dab8~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Emily Mayne Finishes in 2nd Place at PGA National Holiday Open]]></title><description><![CDATA[Student-athlete Emily Mayne finished in 2nd place at the PGA National Holiday Open. After a tough week both mentally and physically,...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/emily-mayne-finishes-in-2nd-place-at-pga-national-holiday-open</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61d347be6adec00016e4a1f3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:06:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_6c02722d30b5431898c551112d168a35~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_640,h_800,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Student-athlete Emily Mayne finished in 2nd place at the PGA National Holiday Open. After a tough week both mentally and physically, Emily traveled to Doral to compete in the Junior Orange Bowl and had to withdraw during the first round due to a shoulder injury.</p>

<p>Emily immediately went to physical therapy and tried her best to recover ahead of the PGA National Holiday Open. Despite not being able to practice or hit balls ahead of the tournament, Emily earned a 2nd place finish.</p>

<p>After the first round, Emily was four shots off the lead and played great golf in the second round to close the lead to just one stroke. Emily has shown tremendous heart to compete while nursing an injury. This is a true testament to Emily's commitment and dedication, and we congratulate her on an incredible performance.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_6c02722d30b5431898c551112d168a35~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_640,h_800,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Walker Faust Finishes in 2nd Place at The Grande Dunes Resort Club]]></title><description><![CDATA[Congratulations to student-athlete Walker Faust for his 2nd place finish at The Grande Dunes Resort Club in Myrtle Beach South Carolina...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/walker-faust-finishes-in-2nd-place-at-the-grande-dunes-resort-club</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61d34512cd6a4c001609a9c9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 18:59:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_daaa26fd575f493a8681c96b907b3a8b~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to student-athlete Walker Faust for his 2nd place finish at The Grande Dunes Resort Club in Myrtle Beach South Carolina on the Hurricane Junior Golf Tour. </p>

<p>Walker shot rounds of 77 and 78 in high winds and rain. His first-round score was the lowest score of both the 14-15 and 16-18 ages divisions. After starting the second round with a bogey and double bogey, Walker kept to his routine and focused on one shot at a time, playing the next 13 holes with 12 pars and one bogey. Walker was able to apply what he’s learned to help navigate and problem solve on the fly to score well and secure a fantastic result.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_daaa26fd575f493a8681c96b907b3a8b~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anne Fernandez Wins Second Place in Texas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Congratulations to student-athlete Anne Fernandez who took second place with the lowest score in the final round to rocket up the...]]></description><link>https://www.albanyacademybahamas.com/post/anne-fernandez-wins-second-place-in-texas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61be510708b10b0016a9a62c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 21:27:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_e6111b7bacde49e48d70287a25f085e2~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Albany Academy</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Congratulations to student-athlete Anne Fernandez who took second place with the lowest score in the final round to rocket up the scoreboard. After eight days of no practice due to the Hero World Challenge at Albany, Anne flew to Texas to compete at the All American Tour - Powered by Mercedes-Benz. Anne endured long travel times and very chilly conditions that were colder than she’s ever played in before. Nonetheless, Anne triumphed with a fantastic final round and adapted to the course and cold weather. Congratulations to Anne on her second-place finish! We look forward to seeing you prepare for a fantastic 2022 season.</p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/3feb3d_e6111b7bacde49e48d70287a25f085e2~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>